<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> - Articles</title>
    <description>Exploring, Experimenting, and Enjoying the little Experiences 💫</description>
    <link>
    http://localhost:4000</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Year in Review 2023</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;2023 had its share of ups and downs, with both joy and sorrow. It brought a mix of emotions and valuable life lessons. I was fortunate to form some fantastic global connections, but I also had to cope with the challenge of letting go of some important people.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2023</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2023</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Year in Review 2022</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;2022 was a year of excitement and exploration. I got to do so many new things and experience life in a different way. Travel was a big part of this year. With the pandemic over, many restrictions were removed, allowing people to travel more freely. I was able to visit the City of Gold - Dubai and also many places in South India. I learned so much during my travels and also got to try so many delicious foods, explore different cultures, and meet new people.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2022</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2022</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Year in Review 2021</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;It was not easy to pen down a review of the year 2021, like I had done for &lt;a href=&quot;https://gopavasanth.github.io/blog/Year-in-Review-2020&quot;&gt;2020&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://gopavasanth.github.io/blog/Year-in-Review-2019&quot;&gt;2019&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2021</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2021</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Taste a cup of tea playing with Arduino</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Vasanth Gopa, joined d-shop, Bangalore as an Associate Software Developer Intern. I was wondering how people create cool hardware contraptions with Arduino and raspberry-pi, so I thought it would be a nice idea to write on after getting my hands dirty exploring these devices. So, the blog post will be revolving around my experience on these devices over a week.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Taste-a-cup-of-tea-playing-with-Arduino</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Taste-a-cup-of-tea-playing-with-Arduino</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>My childhood dream of flying</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;As people usually do, I too had a lot of dreams when I was in school; flying in an airplane, traveling to a foreign country, making a name for myself, to name a few. I am delighted to say that I have brought many of my dreams to fruition during my under graduation in Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham and still continue to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/My-childhood-dream-of-flying</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/My-childhood-dream-of-flying</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Year in Review 2020</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Yet another year comes to a close!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2020</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2020</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Me in WMHACK 2020</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello my dear Wikimedian’s,&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Me-in-WMHACK-2020</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Me-in-WMHACK-2020</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Year in Review 2019</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;2019 was a dream run for me. Traveling, cooking, hiking, coding, mentoring and organizing filled me with tons of joy and made my year beautiful ❤️. An overview of my year is here.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2019</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Year-in-Review-2019</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Into GSoC and WMF Hackathon 2019 !</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Being an undergraduate in Computer Science at Amrita Vishwa Vidyapeetham, over the past couple of years my love for the field of Computer Science has grown exponentially. Being an active member of Free and Open Source(FOSS@Amrita) club at my university, I have acquired a various set of skills including analyzing and debugging of large code bases, developing problem-solving skills and organizing as well coordinating technical events.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Into-GSoC-and-WMF-Hackathon-2019-!</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Into-GSoC-and-WMF-Hackathon-2019-!</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Install MediaWiki in Linux?</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear friends, I’m very happy to see you here, Thank’s for your interest. Let’s start contributing to mediawiki software. Please follow all these steps and do not skip any of the steps, all this process can be completed  in half an hour, In case if you encounter with any errors you can contact me or post a comment in this blogpost anytime,  I will try my best to give provide a  very quick reply.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/How-to-Install-Mediawiki-in-Linux</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/How-to-Install-Mediawiki-in-Linux</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Gitamritam 2k18’Yuva</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the wonderful camp I ever attended before, previously during my school age I attended a yoga camp in 5th standard but this is completely different from all the other camps, I’m here to describe my experience of my Gitamritam camp.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Gitamritam-2k18'Yuva</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Gitamritam-2k18'Yuva</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>FOSS DAYS</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;A club is not just a place to learn, but also a place to share and contribute, Here we indulge ourselves in playing games, conducting debates and explore various places, do gardening, participate in seva, in addition to this we conduct sports and many other activities.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/FOSS-DAYS</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/FOSS-DAYS</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Install Drupal In Your Localhost</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello folks, Today Let’s start contributing to the Open source!  with step by step process&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/How-To-Install-Drupal-In-Your-Localhost</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/How-To-Install-Drupal-In-Your-Localhost</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Trip On Dussehra Vacation</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;On the 28-09-2017 we went to Amma dharshan, After Amma darshan at night 11:00 pm we decided to go to trip and we decided to go trip to kanyakumari on the next day with out any planning we started our journey to kanyakumari , It was so thrilling me to got to Kanyakumari and we reached there by 3:00 pm on that day and after meal we went to Vivekananda Rock Memorial in Boat that was very exiting moment After that we went to watch SUN SET and I am very enthusiastic to see Sunset but the clouds were there so that the sun did not appear properly  and that night we stayed there in a hotel and we watched sunrise that  was really superb! that gave a full satisfaction and then w went to Kanyakumari Mata darshan their we met a man how is selling chains near the beach and that person was very interesting person we really shocked by talking with him He knows many languages (national/international) he  speaks Telugu, Hindi, Malayalam, Kanada, Tamil, French, German… He was the very interesting person as he knows reads Newspaper daily and he is sayisng about Andhra news we shocked by listening to his words and decided to read NEWS paper daily but have to wait and see.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/Trip-On-Dussehra-Vacation</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Trip-On-Dussehra-Vacation</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
